<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sky Travel Blogger</title>
    <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sky Travel Blogger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 08:46:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.skytravelblogger.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Best Things To Do in Cambridge, England</title>
      <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/20-best-things-to-do-in-cambridge-england/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/20-best-things-to-do-in-cambridge-england/</guid>
      <description>Not knowing anything besides Cambridge being a College town, we were in total love with the place. Cambridge is such a beautiful historic town, with a Royal feel to it. Its almost 2 hours away by car from Heathrow Airport, it’s very compact and cozy with many little shops and boutiques. We strolled through the streets and visited so many little stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Fun Things To Do in Punta Cana</title>
      <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/10-fun-things-to-do-in-punta-cana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/10-fun-things-to-do-in-punta-cana/</guid>
      <description>Who would have guessed that Punta Cana in the Dominican Republic would be so scenic. This gorgeous island is filled with Palm trees and Coconut trees. This was a family trip with our family parents and all for as a birthday celebration for my dad who turned 70. This was a fun vacation for all there, children, us and both mine and my husband’s parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grand Sunset Princess Resort in Riviera Maya Cancun</title>
      <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/the-grand-sunset-princess-resort-in-riviera-maya-cancun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/the-grand-sunset-princess-resort-in-riviera-maya-cancun/</guid>
      <description>Picking the right resort is essential when vacationing, and for us the Grand Sunset Princess Resort was perfect. We loved it so much that we recommended it to saw many people who all went there after us.
Right from the moment you walk into the foyer until the time you leave you feel like royalty. First we were greeted with a non alcoholic drink, which was nice and refreshing in the heat, before we even checked in for our room.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>