<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sky Travel Blogger</title>
    <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sky Travel Blogger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.skytravelblogger.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>24 Things to See in London</title>
      <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/24-things-to-see-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/24-things-to-see-in-london/</guid>
      <description>London the city of dreams. It’s the place where everything happens. So many movies are filmed there, books are based there and it’s a place that people love to travel to and its usually a stop over destination to so many countries.
We recently traveled to London with a group of family and friends. Check out my list of must-see places to visit in London and pictures from our travels</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Day - London Itinerary</title>
      <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/5-day-london-itinerary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/5-day-london-itinerary/</guid>
      <description>We stayed in the Westminster District so this itinerary is routed from there, but feel free to adjust from wherever you are staying from
We highly recommend you buy these tickets beforehand for these Attractions if you plan to visit :
 Buckingham Palace Tour Kensington Palace Tour Westminster Abbey London Eye Tower of London Madam Tussaud&amp;rsquo;s St Paul’s Cathedral Book your afternoon Tea experience And which Day tour you decide to do via Viator  Transportation : The easiest mode of Transportation within London is by Underground and/or Bus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Fun Things To Do In Chattanooga</title>
      <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/10-fun-things-to-do-in-chattanooga/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/10-fun-things-to-do-in-chattanooga/</guid>
      <description>Chattanooga is a great vacation spot to get away from the busy life of the neighboring cities and states. Perfect destination especially for us who live in Atlanta because there is so much culture and so many things to do for people of all ages. The night life is great and so many great restaurants to choose from. So many places to visit from art galleries to beautiful scenic gardens and see exotic waterfalls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Getaway – Chattanooga, TN</title>
      <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/chattanoogagetaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/chattanoogagetaway/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it’s the last-minute trips that are so much fun. Fortunately living in Atlanta, Georgia is the perfect distance away from so many nearby states. A holiday weekend approached and deciding what we should do was a small dilemma because we only had 1 night, we could spend away due to a family event that we had committed too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Best Things To Do in Cambridge, England</title>
      <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/20-best-things-to-do-in-cambridge-england/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/20-best-things-to-do-in-cambridge-england/</guid>
      <description>Not knowing anything besides Cambridge being a College town, we were in total love with the place. Cambridge is such a beautiful historic town, with a Royal feel to it. Its almost 2 hours away by car from Heathrow Airport, it’s very compact and cozy with many little shops and boutiques. We strolled through the streets and visited so many little stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Fun Things To Do in Punta Cana</title>
      <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/10-fun-things-to-do-in-punta-cana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/10-fun-things-to-do-in-punta-cana/</guid>
      <description>Who would have guessed that Punta Cana in the Dominican Republic would be so scenic. This gorgeous island is filled with Palm trees and Coconut trees. This was a family trip with our family parents and all for as a birthday celebration for my dad who turned 70. This was a fun vacation for all there, children, us and both mine and my husband’s parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grand Sunset Princess Resort in Riviera Maya Cancun</title>
      <link>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/the-grand-sunset-princess-resort-in-riviera-maya-cancun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skytravelblogger.com/the-grand-sunset-princess-resort-in-riviera-maya-cancun/</guid>
      <description>Picking the right resort is essential when vacationing, and for us the &amp;lt;Princess Punta Cana Hotels&amp;gt;Grand Sunset Princess Resort was perfect. We loved it so much that we recommended it to saw many people who all went there after us.
Right from the moment you walk into the foyer until the time you leave you feel like royalty. First we were greeted with a non alcoholic drink, which was nice and refreshing in the heat, before we even checked in for our room.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>